right there that location is the exact location that i'm describing where site number three
intersects with the morag corridor just west of the spot that i'm talking about where the
machine gun fire where amir was killed that's that's that spot that that machine gun fire
you see coming in is 7.62 machine gun fire from the coaxial machine gun hitting into the crowd
hitting into the dirt you can see the bullets hitting into the dirt and then you can
clearly clearly hear it the bullet the whizzing of the bullets into the crowd that's that's the spot
i'm talking about when amir and this other group of people were running they ran right into that wall
of machine gun fire from the south and it killed them amir laid there dead and to this day his
mother or his stepmother nor his family no one can find him no one's identified his body no one knows
where he is you don't have the ability to inform them even though you saw them you don't have the
ability to inform them because they're cut off they're cut off from communication i mean or that
i don't even know where their where their family might have might have been i don't know if he had
family i don't know if he um i learned through an interview with a woman who said that she was amir
who saw the picture and said that she was amir's stepmother who said that the father had been killed
in an airstrike and that they were separated from amir that day going down to the site because of
the as they were coming to the site there was shooting and the crowd um there was chaos in the
crowd and they got separated from them they're picking up scraps of food they're not picking up
a meal or a box they're picking up scraps yeah so when you also consider the fact that this young
boy amir had to walk eight kilometers to get there he's burned more calories getting to the site
than he'll get in in in six meals in two days worth of food of what's in those boxes that's the cruelty
behind it it's almost like a game kind of like that camp in japan where they were testing that they
did on the chinese experiments on the chinese where they were using very cruel measures to see
how far the human body can go and how how much their mind will push them out of starvation and
then taking some type of satisfaction out of that that's been my assessment of ghf sites from the
beginning this is this is amir and you can see in it this is as he's approaching us in his hands
there he has uh half a part of a bag of of rice that was discarded on the ground he's got a little bag
of uh like a a spilling you know they're falling out of the bottom of the bag here of lentils
he's got some items so the thing is you also have to consider this young 10 year old boy
um who has these raw ingredients that he found how is he going to cook that how is he going to make that
he's got there's no parents with him there was no adults there was no um no nobody with him he was
alone he had no bag either he was just carrying that by hand so he had no bag no box he was carrying
it in his hands but instead it was chosen to put the site eight to ten kilometers away where the
where the people needing the food would have to walk through the fight would have to walk through
the combat why would you do that it's intentional it's deliberate it wasn't an accident so when i
look at these sites my first response to this is like man this is this is a horrible setup man this
is this is bad this is not well it's not a horrible setup it was an exquisitely designed
perfectly executed well-developed concept for genocide yeah i'm going to play a video that i uh
saw this morning i want to play real quick
so you would see that that was commonplace would you witness that that is a ug solutions contractor
an american yeah yeah looks like ice looks like ice in our own streets endless endless amounts of food
and over that fence there's more food just sitting on pallets going nowhere we have soup here
ramen just endless amounts of food it just keeps going when you think it's going to end it keeps
going so much food so he's making the point that look look how much food is in gaza right now
what boer greg pointed out is that that's on the other side of the rafa crossing that's on the other
side of the wall it's not in gaza this is the counter narrative it's embarrassing it's an insult
just and for this individual that's there these people like huckabee and whitkoff and others that
say that there's no starving or there's plenty of food i don't know how they sleep at night i don't
know how they live with themselves i don't know how they look at themselves in the mirror and have any
dignity for who they are as as human beings because there's there's believing a narrative that you want
to believe and then there's just flat out lying to yourself whoever this individual was that was
they're making this video that thinks that that all of us are stupid that oh look at this there's
all this food that they're not trustworthy not only are they not trustworthy they are puppets they are
they are puppets of propaganda to the other side where they they don't know what they're talking about
they go there and they make these assumptions and think that people are just going to believe it
and i'll tell everybody right now whoever filmed that video and them saying that that's in gaza
they're liars yeah and if they want to give me a call and have a discussion about it happy to do
it you're a patriot no doubt it's it's very obvious to me that you're a patriot i love patriots um that
that word has a negative connotation on the left because it's associated with nationalism it's
associated with these foreign wars that we should not have been fighting but i i intend to reclaim
and redesignate that term patriotism because it's been so skewed with nationalism like
with these white supremacist groups these uh like these contractors like you said the um
the infidels uh biker gang uh no doubt if you ask them are you a patriot they'll say yes but they're
not uh neither are the people who kicked you out of these associations who you know they're not patriots
because where i stand if i have to i'll redefine the term as having a very simple meaning
to be a patriot is to love the land a love of the land that your two feet are planted on
and love the human being next to you on that land the other human beings who are also on that land you
care about them you care what happens to them you care about the health of that land and that and
the people who live there you care about it you want what's best it doesn't matter where they're from
what color they are it doesn't matter what language they speak if they're a human being they have a
beating heart and they're on that land you love them and you care about them i am a patriot
and patriotism you know i think that this new brand of a patriot right is someone that calls themselves
an infidel what's a patriot well you you you hate muslims you hate the rest of the world you're always
right your religious position is correct you're a judeo-christian you're right what you believe is
correct and by god you're an american and that's a patriot and that's bullshit to think now that you're
a patriot because what you believe is the truth and what everybody else believes is wrong bullshit
the theft of the perception of a patriot no people people that stand for what's right people that stand
for what's right for their country against popular opinion when needed against what the masses may
think when needed who stand up for what's right that's patriotism 2005 i left the united states as
a christian nationalist before when i went to palestine and i was you know i thought i knew the
definition of patriotism you know i was big on the american flag the judeo-christian narrative of
what america is that kind of thing and then and then i met palestinians and they completely altered
my definition of what a patriot really means their love for their land and their willingness to
sacrifice their bodies for it and the care that they have for the health of that land all the way
from its natural harmonic cycles of you know in nature and agriculture to the way that they care for the
and for the poor and for the stranger who walks on their land to their their reverence to god that
is where i learned what true patriotism means the key point of that is their their treatment of
strangers the way that palestinians treat people who are from out of town to me just stood as being
like one of the most strongest iterations and aspects of patriotism when you treat somebody who is
not from around there or who is unfamiliar whatever you want to call it not from your tribe not from
your village it's a testament to the culture of that land and then that resonates throughout the world
all the way to here in california through myself